Lou Blachly papers, 1827-1965
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series X: Nature Writings, 1948-1964
  - Shore and Water Birds (Notes), undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Southwestern Birds (Notes, Articles, Projected Guide), undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Western Flowers (Notes, Observations), undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Land Birds of the Northeast, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - West Kill, May 9, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Tree Guide (Including Leaf Prints), undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous: Notes, Pictures, Reading Lists, Memos, Correspondence. Includes a copy of Roger T. Peterson's Field Guide to the Birds, 2nd ed., Houghton Mifflin Co., 1947. 1960-1963 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Naming the Birds at a Glance: Birds in Your Binoculars, undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Naming the Birds at a Glance: Instant Identification of Birds, undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Naming the Birds at a Glance: Various Versions of Introduction, undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Naming the Birds at a Glance: Galley, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Naming the Birds at a Glance: Reviews and Fan Mail, undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Naming the Birds at a Glance: Miscellaneous Notes, Versions of Parts. Includes Copy of Published Work Naming the Birds at a Glance by Lou Blachly and Randolph Jenks, Alfred A. Knopf, NY, 1963. Guide Drawings by Sheridan Oman. Also Copy of A Guide to Bird Songs by Areta A. Saunders, Doubleday & Co., NY, 1951. undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Tucson Daily Citizen: Wildflower Series. (Notes, Dummy, Copies as Printed in Booklet Form: Picture Guide to Southern Arizona Wildflowers. undted (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Tucson Daily Citizen: Wildflower Series (Correspondence), undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Tucson Daily Citizen: Wildflower Series (Newspaper Clippings), undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Tucson Daily Citizen: Wildflower Series (Copyright Papers). undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Tucson Daily Citizen: Wildflower Series (Drawings by Sheridan Oman), undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Tucson Daily Citizen: Wildflower Series (Tucson Public School Tests), 1962 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Tucson Daily Citizen: Mammals, Snakes and Lizards Series undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Tucson Daily Citizen: Insect Series. undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Series XI: Miscellaneous Personal Material, 1927-1965
  - Personal Material: Miscellany, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Personal Material: Background and Experience (Summaries Prepared for Various Job Applications), No Date (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Personal Material: Photographs (See Also box 37 for Large Original Drawing of L.B.) undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Personal Material: Miscellaneous Applications for Employment. type="inclusive"normal="1942,1947-1948">1942,1947-1948 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Personal Material: Natalie (Norton) Blachly (Photographs, Miscellaneous Items). undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Personal Material: Insurance Papers, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Personal Material: Medical Bills and Notes, 1941-1964 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Personal Material: Veteran Pension; Income Tax, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Personal Material: Will (Various Versions). undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Personal Material: World War I, undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Personal Material: Clippings, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Personal Material: Chicken and Egg Business (New Mexico), 1950-1956? (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Personal Material: New Mexico (Property, Conservation Council, Miscellaneous Material), undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Personal Material: Radio Programs (New Mexico), 1950's (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Personal Material: Contract with Phyllis Heald, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Personal Material: Organizations and Clubs, undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Personal Material: Christmas Cards, 1958, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Personal Material: L.B.'s Poetry, 1941-1942, 1945, 1948-1964 (Box 31, Folder 1-6)
  - Personal Material: L.B.'s Music, 1917, 1942, 1948-1958, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 7-8)
- Series XII: Diaries, 1920-1965
  - Diaries (Exclusive of 1943-1948, See Boxes 12 and 16), 1920-1950 (Box 32)
  - Diaries (Includes two compositions, Black Mountain Diary, 1952 and On the Upper Rio Grand, July 1956), 1952-April 17, 1957 (Box 33)
  - Diaries, April 18, 1957-July 11, 1959 (Box 34)
  - Diaries, Jul;y 12, 1959-June 23, 1961 (Box 35)
  - Diaries. June 24, 1961-March 24, 1963 (Box 36)
  - Diaries, March 25, 1963-February 1965 (Box 37)
- Series XIII: Oversize Material, 1893-1946
  - Original Drawing of Lou Blachly. (Box 38a)
  - Roadrunner Print by Sheridan Oman. (Box 38a)
  - German Subway Sign Used Near Gruenewald Instructing Post-war Berliners to Remove Wood From Their Shoulders Before Boarding Cars., undated (Box 38a)
  - Broadside: Livery Law. Chapter 62. An Act to Prevent Defrauding of Livery Stable Keepers and Providing Penalty Thereof. H.S.H.B. No. 18, Approved March 14, 1905. (Box 38a)
  - Newspapers: (Box 38a)
    - Aero Corporation of California, (1929)
    - Siam Free Press (Bangkok - Contains Obituary Notice of Sarah B. Bradley),August 8, 1893
    - Lordsburg Liberal(60th Anniversary Edition), November14, 1947
    - Iranian Newspaper in Arabic (Unidentified).undated
    - Alger Republican(Algiers), November 4, 1944.
    - Le Courrier du Maroc (Casablanca), November 4, 1943
    - La Dépêche Algérienne (Algiers),August 16, 1944
    - La Dépêche Marocaine,June 16, 1943
    - Dernière Heure(Constantine), September 16, 1944.
    - Les Dernières Nouvelles (Algiers), July 15, 1943; July 30, 1943, September 18, 1943.
    - Deutsche Allgemeine Zeitung (Berlin),November 5, 1939.
    - L'Echo D'Alger(Algiers),July 10, 1943; September 18, 1943; August 16, 1944.
    - France-Soir(Paris),June 22,1946J
    - Gibralter Chronicle(Gibralter),June 19, 1943
    - Italia Nuova(Rome), February 3, 1945
    - Libé-Soir(Paris), September 1, 1945.
    - Le Maroc Primeuriste: bulletin d'information maraichere:(Casablanca)September 9, 1943
    - Oran RépublicainSeptember 29, 1943
    - Palestine News(Jerusalem), 1944?
    - Palestine News Jerusalem),1944?
    - Palestine Post(Jerusalem), January 16, 1944
    - Paris-Presse(Paris),August 29, 1945
    - >Le Petit Marocain(Casablanca),November 12,1943
    - Stars and Stripes(Africa), September 4, 1943
    - Stars and Stripes(Algiers Daily),July 11, 1943
    - Stars and Stripes (Algiers Daily),September 9, 1943.
    - Stars and Stripes(Algiers Daily),September 17, 1943.
    - Stars and Stripes(Algiers Daily),December 7, 1943
    - Stars and Stripes(Casablanca Daily), November 12, 1943
    - Stars and Stripes Germany Edition),March 17,1946.
    - Stars and Stripes(Mediterranean, November 25,1944
    - Stars and Stripes(Mediterranean)February 13, 1945
    - Stars and Stripes(Mediterranean),March 9,1945
    - Stars and Stripes(Mediterranean), March 10,1945
    - >Stars and Stripes (North Africa), July 31, 1944.
    - Stars and Stripes(Oran Daily),August 9, 1943
    - Stars and Stripes(Oran Daily),September 29-30, 1943
    - Stars and Stripes(Paris Edition),September 3,1943
    - Der Tagesspiegel(Berlin),January 20, 1946.
    - Tunis Telegraph(Union Jack Evening Paper),August 25, 1943
    - Tunis Telegraph(Union Jack Evening Paper), August 27, 1943.
    - Tunis Telegraph(Union Jack Evening Paper), August 30, 1943
    - La Tunisie FrancaiseAugust 30, 1943.
    - Union Jack(First African Edition),August 16,1944.
    - La Vigie Marocaine(Casablanca),November,4,6,1943
  - Three unidentified Maps of German Railway Systems. (Box 38a)
- Series XIV: Oral History Recordings, 1851-1960
  The Oral History collection consists of 625 recordings, which include interviews with pioneers of New Mexico. These interviews are based on the recollections of the early days of New Mexico, New Mexico communities and famous figures including Billy the Kid, Jesse James and Sheriff Pat Garret. Recordings also include Lou Blachly reading from his diary and reading his original poems and compositions
  - I: Beethoven Symphonies 2, 4, 5, 8 with commentary by Lou Blachly (Continued on reel 19), undated (Box 38b, Folder 1, Reel 18)
  - I: Beethoven Symphonies 2, 4, 5, 8 with commentary by Lou Blachly (Continued from reel 18), undated (Box 38b, Folder 1, Reel 19)
  - I: Blachly, Lou, Early Days (Continued on reel 28), undated (Box 38b, Folder 2, Reel 27)
  - I: Blachly, Lou, Early Days (Continued from reel 27), undated (Box 38b, Folder 2, Reel 28)
  - I: Poetry (Lou Blachly Poems, 1947) “There is Blue Sky,” “What is the thing that makes me love,” “I had clean forgot” (Continued on reel 30), June 13, 1954 (Box 38b, Folder 3, Reel 29)
  - I: Poetry (Lou Blachly Poems, 1947) “There is Blue Sky,” “What is the thing that makes me love,” “I had clean forgot” (Continued from reel 31), II: Blachly, Barbara, Diary (Continued on reel 31); June 13, 1954; (January 1 to August 4, 1954) (Box 38b, Folder 3, Reel 30)
  - I: Blachly, Barbara Diary (Continued from Reel 31), January to August 4, 1954 (Box 38b, Folder 4, Reel 31)
  - I: Blachlly, Barbar, Diary (continued on reel 33), January 1- June 19, 1955 (Box 38b, Folder 4, Reel 32)
  - Blachlly, Barbar, Diary (continued from reel 33), January 1- June 19, 1955 (Box 38b, Folder 5, Reel 33)
  - Blachlly, Barbar, Diary (continued on reel 35), June 10-June 31, 1955 (Box 38b, Folder 5, Reel 34)
  - I: Blachlly, Barbar, Diary (continued from reel 34), II: Blachlly, Barbar, Diary (continued on reel 36); June 10-June 31, 1955; January 1 to May 24, 1956 (Box 38b, Folder 6, Reel 35)
  - Blachlly, Barbar,Diary (continued from reel 35 and on 37), January 1 to May 24, 1956 (Box 38b, Folder 6, Reel 36)
  - I: Blachlly, Barbar,Diary (continued from reel 36), II: Blachlly, Barbar - Interview Hurt, Willis, Durip, Ed (continued on reel 38); January 1 to May 24, 1956 (Box 38b, Folder 7, Reel 37)
  - Blachlly, Barbar - Interview Hurt, Willis, Durip, Ed (Duke)(continued from reel 37), Blachlly, Lou - Story of Vermont; undated (Box 38b, Folder 7, Reel 38)
  - I: Blachly, Lou, Story of Vermont, II: Blachlly, Lou, Recollections of Delta Colorado (continued on reel 40); undated (Box 38b, Folder 8, Reel 39)
  - I: Blachlly, Lou, Recollections of Delta Colorado (continued from reel 39 and 41), undated (Box 38b, Folder 8, Reel 40)
  - I: Blachlly, Lou, Recollections of Delta Colorado (continued from reel 40 and on 42), undated (Box 39, Folder 1, Reel 41)
  - I: Blachlly, Lou, Recollections of Delta Colorado (continued from reel 41 and on 43), undated (Box 39, Folder 1, Reel 42)
  - I: Blachlly, Lou, Recollections of Delta Colorado (continued from reel 42), undated (Box 39, Folder 2, Reel 43)
  - History of Delta, Colorado, undated (Box 39, Folder 2, Reel 44)
  - I: Compositions (Lou Blachly), II: Blachly, Early Day in Colorado (continued on reel 46); July 6, 1955; August 2, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 3, Reel 45)
  - I: Blachly, Early Day in Colorado (continued from reel 45 and continued reel 47), August 2, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 3, Reel 46)
  - I: Blachly, Early Day in Colorado (continued from reel 46), August 2, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 4, Reel 47)
  - I: Pioneers Foundation, Inc. (Lou Blachly, secretary,), Record of Pioneer Recordings; Enumeration of Pioneers in Silver City nor recorded,; Reasons for cost of cars; October 29, 1953 (Box 48, Folder 4, Reel 48)
  - Blanchly, Lou, Interim report to Pioneer Foundation Board of Directors enumeration of Pioneers in Silver City (continued on reel 50), November 2, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 5, Reel 49)
  - Blanchly, Lou, Interim report to Pioneer Foundation Board of Directors (continued from reel 49 and on 51), November 2, 1953 (Box 39, Folder  5, Reel 50)
  - Blanchly, Lou, Interim report to Pioneer Foundation Board of Directors (continued from reel 50), November 2, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 6, Reel 51)
  - I: Blachy, Lou, story of the attempt to get support for Pioneer Foundation, October 8, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 6, Reel 52)
  - I: Miscellaneous poems, II: Blachly's interview and recording techniques; III: Stockbridge, Jack - interview lost gold mines in Gila (continued on reel 54),; undated (Box 39, Folder 7, Reel 53)
  - I: Stockbridge, Jack - interview lost gold mines in Gila (continued from reel 53), II: The Museum of the Pioneers, Silver City, New Mexico; III: Songs (whistled) (continued from reel 55),; undated; August 15, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 7, Reel 54)
  - I: Songs (continued from reel 54), II: To Bill, a dairy of Lou Blachly; undated; 1939-1940 (Box 39, Folder 8, Reel 55)
  - I: Dairy of Lou Blachly (continued from reel 55), II: Diary of Lou Blachly, 1944 in North Africa during World War II (continued on reel 57); 1939-1940; April 11, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 8, Reel 56)
  - I: Dairy of Lou Blachy, 1994 in North Africa during World War II(continued from reel 56 and on reel 58, April 11, 1954 (Box 40, Folder 1, Reel 57)
  - I: Dairy of Lou Blachy, 1994 in North Africa during World War II(continued from reel 57), April 11, 1954 (Box 40, Folder 1, Reel 58)
  - Dairy of Lou Blachy, (continued on reel 60) (Box 40, Folder 2, Reel 59)
  - Dairy of Lou Blachy, (continued from reel 59) (Box 40, Folder 2, Reel 60)
  - Diary of Lou Blachly while working as a lookout on Black Mountain in the Gila Forest beginning May 5, 1952 (continued on reel 62), April 5, 1954 (Box 40, Folder 3, Reel 61)
  - Diary of Lou Blachly while working as a lookout on Black Mountain in the Gila Forest beginning May 5, 1952 (continued from reel 62), April 5, 1954 (Box 40, Folder 3, Ree 62)
  - I: Diary of Lou Blachly, II: Songs (whistled); III: Pioneer Foundation Discussion; April 24, 1956; undated; February 19, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 4, Reel 63)
  - Discussion of Wildlife at a Wildlife Refuge, recorded while driving in his car. (continued on reel 65), March 25, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 4, Reel 64)
  - Discussion of Wildlife at a Wildlife Refuge, recorded while driving in his car. (continued from reel 64 and on reel 66), March 25, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 5, Reel 65)
  - I: Discussion of Wildlife at a Wildlife Refuge, recorded while driving in his car. (continued from reel 65), II: Songs sung by Lou Blachy; March 25, 1956; January 29, 1957 (Box 40, Folder 5, Reel 66)
  - I: Songs sung by Lou Blachy and Diary (continued from reel 66), January 29, 1957 (Box 40, Folder 6, Reel 67)
  - I: Recording of flowers in the East (continued) Diary and comments on Algeria (unfinished)(continued on reel 69), May 17, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 6, Reel 68)
  - I: Recording of flowers in the East (continued) Diary and comments on Algeria (unfinished)(continued from reel 68), May 17, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 7, Reel 69)
  - I: Blachy, Lou, Trips to Gila and Cherry Creek, Miscellaneous Poems (continued on reel 70); April 14 and 15, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 7, Reel 70)
  - I: Blachy, Lou, Trips to Gila and Cherry Creek, Miscellaneous Poems (continued from reel 71); April 14 and 15, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 8, Reel 71)
  - I: Blachy, Ralph and Lou songs, Recollections of first flowers identified (continued on reel 73); May 1, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 8, Reel 72)
  - I: Blachy, Ralph and Lou songs, Recollections of first flowers identified (continued from reel 73); May 1, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 1, Reel 73)
  - I: Blachy, Lou trips to Gila, February and March 1956 (Box 41, Folder 1, Reel 74)
  - I: Blachy, Lou trips to Gila, February and March 1956 (Box 41, Folder 2, Reel 75)
  - I: Blachy, Lou, Adventures on Bosque Del Apache National Wildlife Refuge (continued on reel 77), March 23-25, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 2, Reel 76)
  - I: Blachy, Lou, Adventures on Bosque Del Apache National Wildlife Refuge (continued on reel 76), March 23-25, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 3, Reel 77)
  - I: Blachy, Lou, traveling from Albuquerque to Silver City, NM (continued on reel 79), undated (Box 41, Folder 3, Reel 78)
  - I: Blachy, Lou, traveling from Albuquerque to Silver City, NM (continued from reel 78), undated (Box 41, Folder 4, Reel 79)
  - I: Blachy, Lou, narration of visit to Rio Felix and other incidents of the past ten days, June 29th, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 4, Reel 80)
  - I: Blachly, Edward and Lou disclosure on education, March7, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 5, Reel 81)
  - I: Merry Christmas, 1953, (continued on reel 85), undated (Box 41, Folder 5, Reel 84)
  - I: Merry Christmas, 1953, Barb, Bill and Natalie from Lou (continued from reel 84), undated (Box 41, Folder 6, Reel 85)
  - I: Christmas message from Lou(continued on from reel 86), 1955 (Box 41, Folder 7, Reel 87)
  - I: Poetry (48 Lou Blachly Poems), January 8, 1954 (Box 41, Folder 7, Reel 88)
  - I: Poetry (Lou Blachly Poems, 1950-1953), II: Compositions (continued on reel 90); January 1954 (Box 41, Folder 8, Reel 89)
  - I: Compositions (continued from reel 89), II: Compositions and Poetry (Lou Blachly poems) Extracts from "The Mayflower Compact" telling of the Speedwell (continued on reel 91); October 10, 1952 (Box 41, Folder 8, Reel 90)
  - I: Compositions and Poetry (Lou Blachly Poems), II: Compositions and Poetry (Lou Blachly poems) Extracts from "The Mayflower Compact" telling of the Speedwell (continued for, reel 90 and on 92); October 10, 1952; February 27, 1955 (Box 42, Folder 1, Reel 91)
  - I: Compositions and Poetry (Lou Blachly Poems), II: Compositions and Poetry (Lou Blachly poems) Extracts from The Mayflower Compact telling of the Speedwell (continued form, reel 91); II: Song (Lou Blachly),; II: Hughes, Willie - Interview son of outlaw, Jimme Hughes (continued on reel 93); October 10, 1952; February 27, 1955; undated (Box 42, Folder 1, Reel 92)
  - I: Hughes, Willie - Interview son of outlaw, Jimme Hughes (continued from reel 92 and on 94), undated (Box 42, Folder 2, Reel 93)
  - II: Hughes, Willie - Interview son of outlaw, Jimme Hughes (continued from reel 93), Poetry (Lou Blachly Poems, 1947-1948 Where Come these Clouds Berlin revisited,(continued on reel 95; undated; March 1948 (Box 42, Folder 2, Reel 94)
  - I: Poetry(Lou Blachly Poems, 1947-1948 here Come these Clouds Berlin revisited,(continued on reel 95), II: Poetry(Lou Blachly Poems, 1947-1948 The Museum has just been Opened; Together We Could have braved all kinds of Weather (continued on reel 96); March 1948; May 19; March 22, 1947 (Box 42, Folder 3, Reel 95)
  - II: Poetry(Lou Blachly Poems, 1947-1948 The Museum has just been Opened, May 19, Together We Could have braved all kinds of Weather (continued on reel 96) (continued from reel 95); II: Poetry(Lou Blachly Poems, 1945-1946; I Sat on the Bow of the Ship to The Ruins of this City; When I was Young; You, you Million New Yorkers(continued on reel 97); February 13, 1946; February 15, 1946; September 1, 1946 (Box 42, Folder 3, Reel 96)
  - I: Poetry(Lou Blachly Poems,1945-1946, I Sat on the Bow of the ship; The Ruins of this City February 13, 1946; When I was Young February 15, 1946; You, you Million New Yorkers September 1, 1946,(continued from reel 96 and on 98); January 9, 1954 (Box 42, Folder 4, Reel 97)
  - I: Poetry(Lou Blachly Poems,1945-1946, January 9, 1954 (Box 42, Folder 4, Reel 98)
    I Sat on the Bow of the ship,The Ruins of this City,February 13, 1946 When I was Young February 15, 1946 You, you Million New Yorkers September 1, 1946(continued from reel 97)
  - II: Poetry(Lou Blachly Poems,1945-1946, January 8, 1954 (Box 42, Folder 4, Reel 98)
    1941 Biographic sketch from Two Stars and a moon Thru Has it been a year(continued on reel 99)
  - I: Poetry(Lou Blachly Poems,(1941-1943) 1941 Biographic Sketch from Two Stars and a moon Thru Has it been a year?(continued from reel 98) 1943, 1943 from He was always a dreamer(continued on reel 100); January 8, 1954 (Box 42, Folder  5, Reel 99)
  - I: Poetry(Lou Blachly Poems,1941-1943, 1943 from He was always a dreamer(continued from reel 99); II: Poetry(Lou Blachly Poems,1948-1951) October 31, 1948 Listen Intently March 1951 When you lie wasting at eternities gate (continued on reel 101); January 8, 1954; Janauary 7, 1954 (Box 42, Folder 5, Reel 100)
  - Poetry(Lou Blachly Poems,1948-1951), I: Poetry(Lou Blachly Poems,1948-1951) Otober 31,1948 Listen Intently March 1951 When you lie wasting at eternities gate (continued from reel 100); II: Compositions and Comments (Lou Blachly)(continued on reel 102); January 8, 1954; 1954-1955 (Box 42, Folder 6, Reel 101)
  - II: Compositions and Comments (Lou Blachly)(continued from reel 101 and on 103), 1954-1955 (Box 42, Folder 6, Reel 102)
  - I: Compositions and Comments (Lou Blachly)(continued from reel 102), II: Compositions (Lou Blachy)- November 12, 1952 to March 27, 1954(continued on reel 104); 1954-1955; undated (Box 42, Folder 7, Reel 103)
  - Compositions (Lou Blachy) - November 12, 1952 to March 27, 1954 (continued from reel 103), undated (Box 42, Folder 7, Reel 104)
  - Lou Blachy Compositions and reading of poems - 1955 (continued on reel 106), undated (Box 42, Folder 8, Reel 105)
  - I: Lou Blachy Compositions and reading of poems (continued from reel 105), II: Story of Billy the Kid Life and Death - Reminiscences of John P. Meadows as read by Lou Blachly; October 26, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 8, Reel 106)
  - I: Mary Adelle Blachy's own account of marriage and first months in Colorado, undated (Box 43, Folder 1, Reel 107)
  - II: Murder of Will Dover, October 10, 1952 (Box 43, Folder 1, Reel 107)
  - I: Diary of Lou Blachly To others can get the same thrill of discover, July 4 to July 17, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 1, Reel 108)
  - I: Diary of Lou Blachly To Another sunny day to August 2, is my name written there?, undated (Box 43, Folder 2, Reel 109)
  - I: Diary of Lou Blachly August 2 1959 starting is my name written there? to September 13 to the floor got soaked, undated (Box 43, Folder 2, Reel 110)
  - I: Diary of Lou Blachly, through October 13, 1959, undated (Box 43, Folder 3, Reel 111)
  - I: Diary of Lou Blachly, through October 17, 1959 to November 6, 1959 They always have something the matter with them, undated (Box 43, Folder 3, Reel 112)
  - I: Diary of Lou Blachly, through December 4, 1959, undated (Box 43, Folder 4, Reel 113)
  - I: Diary of Lou Blachly, December 5, 1959 to December 24, 1959, undated (Box 43, Folder 4, Reel 114)
  - I: Diary of Lou Blachly, December 25, 1959 through January 19, 1960 It is a pleasant house to look at and Live in, undated (Box 43, Folder 5, Reel 115)
  - I: Diary of Lou Blachly, April 26, 1961 to May 23, 1961 The lizards have discovered, undated (Box 43, Folder 5, Reel 116)
  - I: Diary of Lou Blachly, May 23, 1961 to June 7 1961 to Hauptman's conviction of murder on February 3, 1935, undated (Box 43, Folder 6, Reel 117)
  - I: Blachy, Lou Early days in Colorado (continued on reel 1919), July 27, 1957 (Box 43, Folder 6, Reel 118)
  - I: Blachy, Lou Early days in Colorado (continued from reel 1919), July 27, 1957 (Box 43, Folder 7, Reel 119)
  - I: Bostick, E.C. -Interview, undated (Box 43, Folder 7, Reel 120)
  - I: Bradley, Dwight - Interview Recollections of his father, Dan Freeman-Blachy and Siam, September 24, 1957 (Box 43, Folder 8, Reel 121)
  - I: Bradley, Dan - Interview (Box 43, Folder 8, Reel 122)
    Account of visit to Delta Colorado Account of the Moffat Robbery, September 7, 1893, Denver News and Denver Times to September 11, 1893
  - I: Bratton, Andrew, C. - Interview, undated (Box 44, Folder 1, Reel 123)
    Albuquerque New Mexico, Contracting in Brownwood, Texas, Early days with plumbers, carpenters, bricklayers Coming of Unions Story of Henry Ford who many thought was Jesse James (continued on reel 124)
  - I: Bratton, Andrew, C. - Interview undated (Box 44, Folder 1, Reel 124)
    Albuquerque, New Mexico Contracting in Brownwood, Texas, Early days with plumbers, carpenters, bricklayers Coming of Unions Story of Henry Ford who many thought was Jesse James (Continued from reel 124)
  - II: Bratton, Ethel Mae - Interview, III: Brent, Josh - Interviews (continued on reel 125); undated; May 3, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 1, Reel 124)
  - Brice, Josh - Interview Roswell, New Mexico(continued from reel 124), June 29, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 2, Reel 125)